操你妈的小变态
Fuck you, you little sociopath.
- 听到了吗 Morty - 我知道大家都讨厌我
- You hear this, Morty? - Oh, everybody hates me. I can tell.
- 你们都恨我 - 好了 闭嘴Morty
-Y-You all hate me -- -All right, shut up, Morty.
健康的Rick 我们还搞不搞了
Healthy Rick, are we doing this or what?
嗯 抱歉Morty 你得到亭子里去
Yep. Sorry, Morty. I need you to step into the booth.
别跟那个小没良心的商量 傻缺
Don't negotiate with that little turd, dummy.
你是Rick 该你说了算
You're the Rick. You need to show dominance.
Morty 去亭子里 现在
Morty, booth, now. Booth!
- 来吧 Morty - 别碰我
-Come on, Morty. -Don't touch me!
Morty 这是为你好 主动吸纳这些毒素吧
Morty, do the healthy thing and voluntarily retoxify yourself.
不要啊
Nooooo!
我觉得这样有点性感 这么想好吗
Is it wrong if I think this is kind of hot?
放我出去 Stacy救我 开门
Let me out of here! Stacy, help! Open the door!
你得说出安全词 Morty
I need to hear our safe word, Morty.
海参 海参
Sea Cucumber! Sea Cucumber!
- 你干嘛 - 为了你我什么都愿意 Morty
- What are you doing? - I'll do anything for you, Morty.